I've been in an unknown city with a real in
my pocket and ninety days to set up a business.
I live inside the Chevette and today is twenty-one.
I just pricked the door here,
bro.
The post owner moves good blood.
I should have put on thirty sleeves,
so he said,
it's not complete,
so everything is fine,
man,
it's God himself acting,
right man,
it's about to rotate the month man
let's go to work
that I'm going now.
Clean some windows and clean the chair there,
if you want I can pick it up and start right now.
Closed
talking to the guys who fix the air conditioning.
So man,
if I can get you a client,
you give me a commission.
Bro,
win the ball and get my zap.
Passes quickly.
Have you ever brought a new egg?
Everything is right?
it took
man,
my fifty brother in the window a hundred stories
delivering a pamphlet and I'm going to clean the chair,
my brother.
So what do I do?
Hands over the pamphlet of one eye on the fish and the cat.
Already to do both.
Man I can leave some flags for you haha
It is?
And you don't think that seven hundred reais after twenty days is little,
you think of it now as if it were an objective is accumulation,
yes,
it's little if your box is low,
but your ideas are high.
You can have a lot more money,
understanding that you're investing in the hard strategy,
you have a lot of money there.
And not knowing what to do with it or taking the wrong action.
I'm here, brother.
return,
investment return.
It's calm. See,
things happen,
they don't happen overnight.
Now clean the chair.
So I'll do one before and after.
Here,
in a little while,
I show the result.
Bro count me in there if you need more there.
I got 1 notch of 100 mango malandragem.
You're crazy,
man
Oh what do you think it's over?
I'm going for a dog walk.
Do you have any idea of work there to make 1 quick buck?
Send it in the comments,
please?
Worth it until tomorrow.